We were abandoned.
Abandoned by the devils
whose blood runs through our veins.
That's why we're forced
to live in this walled ghetto.
And it's why your father isn't here.
Your father is Marleyan.
So it's against the
rules for him to be with us.
If only we were Marleyan...
Oh, yeah. Back then...
I strove to be a Warrior so Mom and I
could become Marleyans.
Who said you could walk?
Faster! Run,
you filthy seed of swine!
Don't you wanna become
Honorary Marleyans?
Did you guys hear?
In just a few years, we'll be
sent to attack Paradis Island.
It's almost time
for us to inherit our Titans.
Out of us seven,
six'll be made Warriors at once.
No way! I'll finally
become Marleyan!
Huh? What're you excited for?
If anyone's getting
left behind, it's you.
What?
What do you got
that the rest of us don't?
Huh?
Are you real strong? Real smart?
A crack shot?
Good in a fight maybe?
No. You only made it
this far by constantly
going on about your love for Marley.
"Yes, sir, I'll slaughter
those island devils
just as soon as I've licked
your boots cle... "Hey!
Are you seriously insulting our mission?
How dare you!
You almost sound like
a stray Restorationist.
Huh?!
You traitor. I knew it!
I'll report you to
the commander for this!
Report this... you little shit!
Well? Want more?
He's had enough, Porco!
Anyone can whine about
how much they hate the island.
That's why you'll be doing it
here for the next 13 years.
Porco!
Come on, Pieck, let's go.
Hurry after us as soon as
you're done crying.
I'll catch another
beating if you're late.
Reiner. I'm sorry.
Get up, Reiner. Here.
I have to become a Marleyan,
so I can live with my mom and dad.
I can't wait 13 years.
But, it's like he said,
I... I'm weak.
It isn't gonna be
Porco's decision to make.
And well, loyalty's more
important than he might think.
Right? Annie?
Huh? Dunno. I was distracted.
So this goal.
Are you sure it's what you want?
Huh?
You get 13 years, and that's it.
But I'll be a hero for every one of them.
If I can defeat the devils on Paradis,
I'll have saved the whole world.
And after that, my parents'll
be proud to call me son.
I wish something would happen.
Eren! I finally found you!
Incredible.
They're even stronger than expected.
The Female Titan.
Its greatest strength is its versatility.
Not only does it boast a combination of
high mobility and endurance,
its hardened strikes are
incredibly destructive.
It's also able to summon Pure Titans.
Though its range is limited.
Leonhart is perfect.
The Armored Titan naturally
specializes in defense.
But if it charges at full speed,
it can break through
gates and walls alike.
As Marley's shield,
it needs to stand tall
where the fighting is thickest.
It suits Braun's tenacious spirit.
The Jaw Titan is an assault weapon.
It's as speedy as it is small,
with powerful claws and teeth
that can crush almost anything.
Marcel's sharp enough to keep up with it.
The Beast Titan is more potent than ever.
It's large and strong,
but more importantly,
it can outperform an artillery unit
with nothing but a fistful of rock.
What's more,
its greatest power lies in its blood.
The Cart Titan's outstanding endurance
makes it well-suited for
lengthy missions on the field.
Because it can hold
its form for days on end,
we've enhanced it with
specialized equipment.
Pieck's superior judgment
will serve well here.
Finally, there's the Colossal Titan.
It is a god of destruction.
We trust that Hoover can handle it.
I feel bad for those island devils.
That monster will appear from thin air
and start killing them someday.
We've been training the
members of this Warrior Unit
since they were practically infants,
and it's clear that
they're stronger for it.
But why send these children
to take the Founding Titan?
Frankly, I think it's a bit insane.
You think so? I'm not so sure.
We did just watch these children
bring a nation to its knees.
It makes no sense!
You're obviously at
the bottom of the group.
So why would they pick you?
Heh. Haven't you figured it out?
You're at the bottom. "Pock."
You little...!
Porco, stop! Calm down.
You don't want to defy the brass.
Reiner. I'm sorry.
Dad!
It's you, right?
My mom used to work at this barracks
a good while before I was born.
You would've met her here.
Her name's Karina Braun!
Look at my armband!
Mom has one, too.
We're Honorary Marleyans.
Now we can all live toge...
The hell's wrong with you?
What, did that woman send you here?
Guess she wants
revenge on me. Shit!
She forced you to become
a Warrior just for that?
If they find out where you're
from, my family's screwed.
So you're trying to get
me hanged, is that it?
Well I'm running away as fast as I can.
Away from you and
your damned Eldian mother!
Reiner! Reiner!
I'll be waiting for you, sweetie!
That's right.
Even if I don't have a dad,
I was chosen to wield the Armored Titan.
I'll save everyone from the island devils
and become a hero to the world.
It's tough to cover
much ground, moving at night.
Yeah, especially when it's this cloudy.
We're sure the king won't
use the Founding Titan?
I don't get it.
If we blatantly attack his walls, then...
What's the point in asking now?
Just put your faith in Marley's research.
That's right.
There's no turning back.
When we reach the wall
tomorrow, we'll have to...
Huh? What's wrong?
Don't tell me you're feeling
hesitant to kill these devils.
They're a threat to our entire world!
But the greatest nation in
the world chose us to save it.
To punish these devils for their crimes!
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Listen, Reiner.
The truth of it is,
you were never supposed to be chosen.
I influenced the army's decision
by making my little brother look bad,
and putting you up on a pedestal.
Sorry. I only did it so
that he would... be safe...
I'm sorry... Reiner...
Why?
Why are you apologizing?
Bertholdt! Annie!
Marcel...
They're gone. They were
all eaten because of me.
And I'll be next.
I... I'm gonna die here.
Not bad. You just beat me
in a long-distance race.
You've never done that before.
If we had transformed
and defended ourselves,
we wouldn't have lost the Jaw Titan.
Ugh. Well. Shit.
He's gone for good now.
There weren't supposed to be any Titans
this far from the walls, though.
We need to go back.
Let's track down Jaws and leave.
The Titan that ate Marcel
should be human again.
C'mon. Without Marcel to
lead us, this mission's doomed.
Wait. We can't. We can't!
We can't go!
We gotta continue the mission as planned.
Oh, yeah. If you go back now,
you'll be stripped of the Armor.
The next Warrior will eat you.
Though that isn't really
a problem for me.
You think it'd just be me?
Huh?
You and Bertholdt ran away, too,
so why would I take all of the blame?
What makes you so confident that you two
won't get eaten right along with me?
Going after Jaws isn't
a good idea, anyway.
If they use its power to run, that's it.
Our Titans are way too
slow to catch up to it.
But how could someone learn
to use it that quickly?
You mastered the Colossal on
your first try, so you tell me!
Anyway, if we go to the dock
as failures, we're doomed!
We need the Founding Titan.
There's no going home without it!
You know. If you had been
even a fraction this composed
when that Titan came at us,
we wouldn't have had to
lose the Jaw Titan or Marcel.
So, you think the two of us'll be blamed
for running after you, huh?
Well, then why don't you
come clean to Magath?
It's your fault this happened,
so own up to it!
We're not heroes, dumbass.
The Marleyans just see us as weapons.
Understand? They lied!
Marleyan or Eldian, they're all
just in it for themselves!
And guess what?
I'm the same:
I've gotta get home alive!
If you feel guilty
about Marcel, then die!
Take all of the blame and die!
Reiner is dead.
If we need Marcel, then he's who I'll be.
Stop. Let her go.
If we wanna make it
back, this is our only hope.
Once our mission is done, we can go home.
I wanted to become a Warrior,
because I thought it
would make my mom's wish
to live with me and my father come true.
But, my father never
wanted any part of us.
Mom lived for a dream
that she knew was hopeless.
I should've never been chosen.
I should have died today.
Why apologize?
And why save someone like me?
This can't end with me doing nothing.
Knowing nothing.
Before I die, I need to change something!
Where are we?
In Wall Rose. We're safe.
Annie. Bertholdt. I'm sorry.
I'll be the Warrior
I should've been... for Marcel.
Oxface! Just what in the
hell did you come here to do?
I'm here to save humanity.
My village was in the southeast
mountains of Wall Maria.
For us, it happened at dawn.
The animals were all makin' a racket.
On top of that, I heard
a strange rumbling.
I realized it was footsteps
and opened the window to look.
What happened next is a blur,
but I got away
on my horse. Alone.
Leaving behind three kids
right about your age.
Hello there, missy.
You must be a girl of refined taste
to take such an interest
in this old geezer.
I was born at the inn my mom worked at.
She only met my father once,
but she described him to me in detail,
so that I'd know you when I saw you.
Well, ain't that a touchin' story.
If ya wanna give your daddy
a hug, then put your hands up.
How can you be so sure
that it isn't true?
I made my sister a promise,
so this tale of yours is a joke,
and a shit one at that.
You're so mean. Daddy!
Well, damn. Seems you've
hit your rebellious phase.
Come back!
Huh. That's a new one.
His legs are saying
it'll snow today, right?
Yeah, but his torso's saying clear skies.
Call it hail and get moving
or you'll be late for muster.
Bertholdt! Wake up!
While you two slept like babies
after playing with your "friends,"
I was crawling around
the capital's sewers.
But I hit my limit.
Almost got caught.
Your limit, huh?
Let's cut our losses and take
what we know back to Marley.
At this point, I bet they'll
be happy to hear anything.
No. After five years,
they'll be expecting a lot more
than a few scraps of information.
All right, asshole.
Do you have a plan?
Yeah. We breach Wall Rose.
It's the best chance we have of
smoking out the Founding Titan.
It also means killing
a lot of your friends.
I keep telling you, Annie.
The cadets aren't our
friends. They're devils.
But it can't hurt to gain their
trust, so I wish you'd act
a little less standoff-ish.
Let them think you're one...
I'm gonna puke.
Could you please move
your face away from mine?
You're exhausted.
I'm sorry for laying so many
burdens on you, Annie.
Let's call it a night.
I, uh... I keep
having this dream.
Where I see that guy from the
mountains who hung himself.
He must've been planning to do it.
So why did he tell us his story first?
Eren. Don't kill yourself.
Take a break.
Shit! Hey, Reiner.
How'd you get so strong?
What do I need to do to
be like you or Mikasa?
I've gotta change,
or I'll die without
accomplishing a damn thing.
Just do what you have to.
Keep moving forward.
That's all we can do.
Right. Thanks for the advice.
You're gonna butcher
all the Titans, right?
I'm sure you can do it.
Damn it. If nothing
changes, then...
That's right.
I still have... them.
The hospital.
Hey!
So, you're able to talk now, huh?
Guess that means you're recovering.
Eh. This place is for
treating psychological wounds,
but mine are fake.
Huh?
I said that I forgot where
I came from due to amnesia,
but I just don't wanna go back.
I'm not quite ready
to face my family yet.
Will you report me?
No, I wouldn't do that.
You're all beat up.
Guess that's from your Warrior training?
Yeah, but honestly, it's pointless.
There's another candidate
who's way better than me.
So there's no way that I'll be chosen.
I'm glad to hear it.
Huh?
You're a good person.
I hope you'll get to live a long life.
Thing is, I don't want this
other candidate to be picked.
Why not?
Is this rival of yours a girl by chance?
She's famous around here.
She did incredible things in the war.
Ask anyone, and they'll tell you
that she should be the next Armor.
It doesn't matter what I want.
'Cause I can't do a damn thing about it.
Every day I've spent here, I've wondered.
How did all these people
let it come to this?
Minds and bodies ruined.
Dreams of freedom erased.
Personalities burned away.
No one would want to go to war
if they knew what it would do to them.
But it's not like we all
leapt into that hell knowingly.
Most of us were pushed.
Some of us were pushed by other people.
And some of us were pushed by
the environments we grew up in.
So, the few who do
choose to leap into hell
see it differently than the rest.
And they're also able to see
something beyond the hell.
Maybe that something is hope.
Or maybe it's just another hell.
Fact is, you can only
find out by moving forward.
Magath joins hands with the Tybur family
and readies the army
for a fateful speech.
As the festival enlivens the city,
Reiner is surprised
by a face from his past.
Next episode:
"From One Hand to Another."